- Aw. He's using his jacket
as some kind of
security blanket.
- That's so cute and pathetic.
- It really is.
You do you. weirdo!
- Oh. hey. guys. I'm just
sucking on my jacket.
A Clump-O-Honey candy
got stuck right there
over a thousand years ago.
and I can still taste it.
- You know who I bet
would like some of that?
Me! Zoidberg.
Oh. no!
Zoidberg. you residue hog!
Now all I taste is crab juice.
- So. buy another jacket candy.
- I can't. They
stopped making it
after it got reclassified
as industrial glue.
- Ah. Then I. Bender.
will recreate the recipe.
Don't forget. I came in
third on MasterChef Junior.
- May I have a taste?
- Sure. You seem like the
kind of guy who has a mouth.
- Whoa! Diabetic coma!
- Hm. I better add some
sugar to make it less sweet.
- And just a touch of treacle
to remind me of my dear
departed Aunt Juanita.
She
drowned in treacle.
- You know I'm
dying on the floor.
So. what do you think?
- Mm! It's perfect. Bender.
Totally jacket worthy.
It's a little sticky.
It's
a lot sticky!
And there's
something hard in it.
- Luckily. I'm an expert
at fixing human beak bones.
Are you free Friday for
an expensive appointment?
- Let me check. Open calendar!
Shmeird. There's
some old alert
I set up 20 years ago.
Our babies?!
- It's time. my love.
- Oh. Kif!
- The hell are
you talking about?
Something to do with
the meatbag life cycle?
- That's right.
Bender. Many years ago.
I gave birth to a
clutch of tadpoles
with Amy by my side.
- I have video of the
birth. Wanna see it?
No!
- That is the wrong
kind of delivery!
Oh. Nelly! Oh!
- Life is disgusting.
- No. it was beautiful.
But I was so not
prepared to be a mother.
- In 20 years.
they'll sprout legs
and crawl back onto
land as children.
- I'll be ready then.
- Well. Amy. are you ready now?
- Having a family with you
is the only thing I
want in the whole world.
- Then can I have your car?
- No!
- Too late. I
already crashed it.
- Oh. this is so exciting!
The birth ceremony
will begin any minute.
- Thanks for the warning.
And don't describe it
to me!
- We're here!
- Mom! Dad!
Oh. I'm so glad you made it!
- Oh. we wouldn't miss the
birth of our grandbabies
for a million dollars.
- 'Cause we're so rich.
that's like a penny.
- Oh. my. It's
the Grand Midwife.
- I am the Grand Midwife!
- Big fan!
- I am Kif of the clan Kroker.
- I know. I recognize your head.
- And this is my smizmar. Amy.
We have come to
receive our offspring.
- As you transition
to parenthood.
I shall be your
counsel and guide.
I do so out of solemn
respect for our traditions
and not for any
optional cash donation
people sometimes
place in that basket.
- Thank you.
- It's green.
and there's a little sign on it.
- Found it!
- Then the Emergence
shall now commence!
Or not. It's unpredictable.
Guess I'll have to wing it.
Anybody here from out of town?
O-oh!
Here they come.
- Oh my. I'm so anxious. my
camouflage reflex is kicking in.
- No. it's helpful.
I wanna look cute for
our hundreds of kids.
- We shall now stand
by. without interfering.
as we observe the sacred
process known as...
the Winnowing.
- What's that mean?
- It means don't
start naming them yet.
- Four of them made it!
Well. three and a half.
- Young creatures
of the Black Lagoon.
go now to your parents.
- Uh. can I help you?
- Over here!
They're perfect.
- Ew. She's touching them.
- Cherish these
children. Kif and Amy.
for they are beautiful.
Eh...
- Well. in-in the sense that
all children are beautiful.
The transformation is complete!
We welcome these new
beings of the land.
- They can call
me Captain Uncle.
- Uh. I'll go dispose
of this medical waste.
With a little butter and lemon.
- Want a picture with the kids?
- No need.
The way they look is
burned into my mind.
- They're nice. you know?
Just a kinda little...
- Super gross.
- But. you're
finally grandparents.
- That'll be our little secret.
Oh my.
- Thanks for bringing the
kids by for my lunch break.
- They're the sweetest
thing on the menu.
Not even close!
- Uh. question.
These three babies are
totally different sizes.
Question mark.
- Oh. well. they
grew at varying rates
depending on the temperature
of the water they were in.
Little Newt here was
in a cold. deep area.
- Mama!
- Wrong again.
- Mandy is from the
temperate middle depths.
- He's shrively!
You haven't
seen the half of it.
- And Axl is from
the warm shallows.
just like his old man.
Do you always
have to talk about me?
- So why does this one
keep calling me Mama?
And what's with
the big weird eye?
- It's not weird.
It looks like yours.
It's pretty weird.
- Why would he look like me?
- Don't you remember?
Twenty years ago.
you impregnated Kif.
- Seriously? Oh. my God.
I must have been super drunk.
- Leela. you bone brain!
You didn't have sex.
Bone.
- Luckily. there's
an educational movie
that explains how Kif's
species reproduces.
And it's filthy.
YowzaVision
Educational Films
presents Sex Across
The Universe.
Oh. yeah!
Educate me. baby.
This week.
the Amphibiosans.
For every organism
across the universe.
reproduction is a
steamy. erotic process.
Except the Amphibiosans.
They just barely touch hands
while the rest of us
are gettin' it on.
Yowza.
Eh. that
was pretty hot.
- So. you see. Amy
was my smizmar.
the one whose mere presence
made me receptive to pregnancy.
- Which makes me their smizmama.
- But it was Lila who
contributed the DNA
when she accidentally
touched Kif's hand.
- Are you sure I wasn't drunk?
I-I mean. I'm drunk
now.
- Mwah!
- Ew! Mom. Dad!
Leela!
♪ Will you stay in
our lovers' story? ♪
♪ If you stay. you
won't be sorry ♪
♪ 'Cause we believe in you ♪
♪ Soon you'll grow.
so take a chance ♪
♪ With a couple of kooks
hung up on romancing ♪
♪ Will you stay in
our lovers' story? ♪
♪ If you stay. you
won't be sorry ♪
♪ 'Cause we believe in you ♪
♪ Soon. you'll grow.
so take a chance ♪
♪ With a couple of kooks ♪
♪ Hung up on romancing ♪
- Let's reinflate
my head and go home.
- Yeah. Maybe they'll conk out
and we'll get a little us time.
Those little guys are
the best. but they're a lot.
- Well. luckily. there's
two of us to split the work.
♪ Doop. doo-doo-doop.
doop. doop. doop. doop! ♪
- Captain Brannigan!
At your service. sir.
- With ease. Lieutenant. I have
a bit of news to say at you.
- Is it about the baby gifts you claim
you sent? Because we still haven't...
- I'm afraid there's
no time to discuss
the many presents I bought.
some of which are large.
Soldier. you are ordered
to report for duty.
- Is it war?
- I hope so. but we're not sure.
All we know is that DOOP
has lost radio contact
with a remote outpost in
Ursa Major. Over and under.
- I'm sorry you'll have
to handle the kids alone.
I'm not worried.
I love you!
- Roll call!
"Four eyes."
"One-eye." "Crab man."
"Can man." "Who cares?"
Dammit! Where's Amy?
What do I need. a bigger antler?
Oh. I'm so. so sorry.
The babysitter didn't show up.
Ah!
- Finally. Where are you?
- Sorry. toots.
I must have the address wrong.
784 West 28th Street?
Uh-huh. Weird.
th-that's what I got.
Oh. Earth! Ah!
Coulda swore you
said Kepler 10B.
Guess I'll catch the next
generation ship back to Nutley.
- Oh...
- Mom. Mom. Mom! Can you
judge our whispering contest?
Okay. You ready?
I lose!
Oh. come on! Oh...
- Look at me. chugging
mineral water on a weeknight!
So wild and free!
I miss them so.
- I feel you. soldier.
And not in a handsy
way this time.
Mm.
Sticky...
Bring a bowl of these
candies to my quarters
when you're done crying.
- Thanks for offering to
watch the kids. Leela.
I need a break so
bad. You have no idea.
- No. it's clear you're
a wreck. and I get it.
They're a nightmare.
A-A sweet. adorable nightmare.
- That's fair. Kids!
Mommy's gonna go nap-nap.
Don't be scared of
Leela. She's very...
Yay! Mommy Leela!
Cowabunga. dude!
- The Clump-O-Honeys you
requested. Capt... Oh jeez.
If there's nothing further. I will...
- Oh no. you willn't.
These delicious Clumps
aren't for eating. Mm!
Mm...
They're for manscaping.
Manscape me. Kif.
That's an order.
Owooga!
- Ooh!
- Whoa! What's that?
- I never saw one
of those before.
and I was born.
like. four days ago.
- It's a ship loader.
Any hyperactive kids here
up for a nice. exhausting
treadmill race?
Oh wow! Cool! I mean. cool.
- God. I hope this works.
- Approaching the outpost. sir.
Still no response on any frequency.
- My God. What the hell
happened down there?
It looks like the whole
planet has psoriasis.
- You're looking at the
back of my head. sir.
- Welcome to
Exobiology Station 38.
- Dammit! I'm outta laser!
- Um. hello. sir. Is
this outpost secure?
The DOOP hasn't received any
response from you in months.
- Oh. yeah. Transmitter
got ripped up by bears.
That's what we study here.
Bears. I'm a bear biologist.
- Sounds like a fun
job that pays bad.
- I used to be a whale
biologist. but I hate whales.
Hate them.
- Well. then it's good you
found an animal you like.
- Nope. Still looking.
This bear
species is known as tardigrades.
It's a fancy word for ugly.
Oh. shut
up. you stupid bear!
They're also stupid. by the way.
I discovered that.
Bear biologist.
I fixed the transmitter.
Now. may I please head
home to my family?
- Without delay. But first.
candy break?
- Are you bat crackers?
If they smell human food.
they go bat crackers!
- It seems they recognize
a fellow apex predator.
Well. four can
play at that game.
Kif! Help!
Let's
go! Faster! Faster!
Go. horseface. go!
Neigh!
Now. buy us ice cream!
Rum raisin tastes just
like caterpillars!
- We love you. Leela.
- Aw. hell no! You're
not the mom of them!
- What?
- Are you done spoiling my kids rotten
so they'll love you more?
- I'm just a beaten-down horse.
- Well. you can trot
back to the barn now!
Kif's coming home soon.
and you are not their mom!
- Uh. actually. I sort of am.
- Go on! Git! Hyah!
Oh God. they're nuzzling me!
Hello?
- Please come home. Kiffy!
The kids like Leela more
than me. and it really hurts.
I'm the worst mom ever.
Except for my own mom.
Stop licking my
velour! It's dry clean only!
- Amy. darling. the
children love you.
And I love you.
And stay away
from my scrotums!
- You're their mother.
and you always will be.
Nothing can change that.
- Amy Wong. a challenge
has been filed
for the motherhood
of these children.
No...
Amy? Amy.
I'm coming home. I swear.
I have to leave right now. sir!
No. Kif! The DOOP
never leaves a man behind!
Not when I'm the man!
- Alright. bears. Daddy's
coming to tuck you in...
to your graves.
- I'll be out here.
- Nobody's taking my babies!
They're everything to me!
- I appreciate your emotional
shouting in my ear hole.
but I must intervene whenever
parenthood is called into question.
- Grand Midwife?
- Oh. drop the
surprised act. Leela.
How could you do this?
- Do what?
Suck the jelly out of the
jelly donuts with a straw?
- This jelly hound did not summon
me. The challenge is automatic
when tests show the
smizmar contributed no DNA.
The children
inherited genes
only from Kif and Leela.
plus trace DNA from
a certain Scruffy.
Scruffy's stuff gets around.
- Should the challenge indicate
someone else is the mother.
then that person...
eh. or whatever...
shall raise the children.
- But... But...
- You and Kif must be present for
the challenge tomorrow. Good day.
Yeah. FYI. y-you've got a
little jelly right there.
- Did somebody call
an exterminator?
- It's been a blast.
- Help me. Kif!
They found the secret
candy in my girdle!
I'm a camouflaged
killing machine.
- I'm...
I'm sorry I got
so jealous. Leela.
I just kinda lost it.
- It's okay.
The bond parents feel with
their kids is intense...
so I hear.
I'm just
proud I helped you become a mom.
I hope it works out
for you tomorrow.
- And if it doesn't.
I'm sure you'll
take good care of them.
- I refuse to die groveling.
But I'm open to sniveling.
Naked Kif.
you saved my life!
You have my undying loyalty.
Eat Kif! He's boneless!
- This one's for Axl. Mandy.
and little what's-his-name.
- I am the Grand Midwife
from the other day.
inquisitor for the
challenge of Amy Wong.
Amy. where is your smizmale?
- He isn't with me.
- Oh. the sorrow! Oh. the shame!
- There he is!
- Okay. but it doesn't
lessen the shame.
- Kif!
- Amy!
Daddy!
- I don't remember him.
- So. like. did
you do war stuff?
- I did what a Daddy had to do.
- Bear number 23
was also stupid.
fighting for scraps while
I dined on salmon tartare.
None for you. losers!
Oh!
- The challenge may play
out over days or weeks
within the brutal confines
of the Inquisidome.
Some call it a tiki hut.
- Leela's gonna watch you
guys while we're in there.
And maybe a little longer.
But whatever happens.
you're going to be okay.
- You are. too.
- The challenge is a
challenging challenge.
dating from when our
language had few words.
It will incorporate a
battery of genetic tests
and a full neuropsychological
obstacle course.
but it begins with
a simple question.
Amy Wong.
Do you or do you not
love those children?
- More than I knew I
could love anything.
- Which is all
that truly matters.
The challenge is over.
You are their mother
and always will be.
Oops! That wasn't
supposed to happen.
Cheap. lousy wall.
Children! You may now come
hug your mother and father.
For only a small additional fee.
- You're my favorite mommy.
- Who wants treacle?
- Strong stuff. huh?